[Music]
What's up?
We're
[Music]
not
We the winner.
[Music]
Who when I
wait
for
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Can you lift up your hands to the Lord
and just thank him for being a good
God, a good father who loves us and who
cares for us? Just raise your voice and
thank him. Lord, we want to thank
you. We thank you for being a good
God. We thank you for your
grace. Thank you for your
mercy. Thank you for your
kindness. Thank you for your power
that's able to keep
us. Tell him how much we appreciate him
today. Bless your name, oh Lord.
Bless your name, oh
Lord. Bless your name, oh
[Music]
Lord. Thank you,
Jesus. And now, Lord, as we stand here
today, we want to thank you for who you
are. We want to thank you for being a
good God who's worthy of the praise and
the honor. We remember
today the resurrection of our Lord Jesus
Christ. And because he rose from the
dead, we stand victorious in your name.
We give you praise and honor in Jesus
name we pray. And everybody
said, and everybody shouted and
said, "Before you sit down, why don't
you go to five people, give them a high
five, tell them Jesus rose from the
dead, and that's why we're here
today." Oh yeah. Jesus rose from the
dead. Amen.
[Music]
Amen. Orlando
stadium. We'd love to welcome everyone
of you as you all have been welcomed and
uh we have received you and uh we also
do want to
acknowledge Minister Paktau the minister
of trade and industry who's here with us
today. uh would love to welcome you
minister sir. Thank you for being here
with us and as well we've also
recognized the presence of uh honorable
bongos MC who are the e government and
uh would love to welcome you uh our
honorable MC. Can you give our MC a big
hand please? Everybody they are seated
over
there. We love to thank pastor B
Pritorius together with your
entourage ka le mama and the guests and
then we have Dr. Goodwill Gurubani Grace
Family of
Churches forward to see Posh Balala with
his wife and the family and we have oh
pastor Filimoni who's here as well
pastor toani house of
glory
mama le the wife and the members of the
church here they are here wow we are so
grateful and then we have Mrs. Bua and
family and Maliba together with the
family and everybody who is here today.
Can you give our guest a big hand and
give yourselves a big hand as
[Applause]
[Music]
well? I think the prophella says a
better amen than the
people.
Amen. Our scripture reading is in Luke
24.
It's a bit long, but I need to read all
of
it from verse one to verse
9. We read in the New King James
Bible. Now on the first day of the week,
very early in the
morning. They and certain other women
with them came to the
tomb bringing the spices which they had
prepared.
But they found the
stone rolled away from the
tomb. Then they went in and didn't find
the body of the Lord
Jesus. And it happened as they were
greatly perplexed. If you are able to
underline that or mark that, just do
that. as they were greatly perplexed
about this that behold two men stood by
in shining
garments that as they were afraid and
bowed their faces to the earth they said
to
them why are you looking for the living
among the
dead is not
here but he is risen
Remember how he spoke to you when he was
in still in
Galilee, saying the son of man must be
delivered into the hands of sinful men
and be crucified and on the third day he
will rise
again and they remembered his words. May
the Lord bless the reading of his word
and everybody said amen.
I want to point out as well that we will
be making reference to Matthew
28 and this story also appears in Mark
16 and John 20. I won't read
those. We'll make reference to these as
we look at certain expressions about the
resurrection of our Lord Jesus Christ. A
second scripture is in Romans chapter 8
just one verse verse
11. But if the spirit of
him who made Jesus come again from the
dead is in
you, he who made Christ Jesus come again
from the dead will in the same
way through his spirit which is in
you give life to your bodies which now
are under the power of death.
May the Lord bless the reading of his
word again. Can I hear an amen?
This Sunday, I want to talk
about living in
resurrection life.
We're going to look at the story of the
resurrection of our Lord Jesus
Christ and run that parallel to what
does it mean when Paul says if the
spirit of him who raised Christ from the
dead dwells in us that same spirit will
bring resurrection life.
Today being Sunday and in other parts of
the world, this particular
Sunday, the Christian
community congregates in many different
places, in churches, in
halls, in our country, under trees,
under bridges, in open spaces, and this
morning in the
stadium. We congregate here on
Sunday which is something that we do as
the Christian community to congregate on
Sunday. And the reason for that is that
Sunday is the actual day where as we
read in
scripture the women discovered that
Jesus had been raised from the dead.
I want us to examine this
truth on the two levels.
We will detail the facts and the story
of
resurrection. But then we will ask that
question, how does that resurrection
work in my life and how does it benefit
me? If you were to visit the holy land,
one of the historical sites which is
worth visiting is called the church of
the sepulka in
Jerusalem. The word sepulka simply means
tomb.
This is a place that was recognized as
an authentic
place of the resurrection of Jesus way
back in
3:26. And it's recognized as that place
where the tomb of Jesus was and where he
was raised from the dead. In Matthew 28
and Luke
24, we note that it was Mary
Magdalene and another Mary that the
Bible said they went on Sunday morning
to visit the tomb or the sepila of Jesus
Christ.
It was at the dawn of
day. And so they
went to go and check the tomb because in
previous verses we note that after Jesus
died, he was buried according to the
rituals of the day. His body was
embarmed. His body was prepared. He was
wrapped in grave clothes. Placed in this
tomb.
So they they came on this particular day
just to check on him and to make sure
everything is
okay. But then a series of things
happened as they came to the
tomb. They found the tomb
empty. But they were not the only ones
who found who encountered the
resurrection of Jesus.
We know that there were several
witnesses that could attest to the
resurrection of
Jesus. The first
witnesses was the
angels because when Jesus was raised
from the dead, the angels were there. As
a matter of fact, when the women came
into the tomb, they found an angel
there. And it was the angel who asked
them, "Why are you looking for the
living among the
dead?" The second witness to the
resurrection of Jesus were the Roman
soldiers. I'll explain that more in
time. They were stationed to guard the
tomb to make sure that nobody disturbed
the contents inside the tomb. In fact,
the reason these soldiers were
there was because the religious leaders
of the
day said to themselves, "This man who is
a
blasphemer, he went around telling his
followers that he's going to be raised
from the
dead. We want to make sure that his
followers don't come and steal his body
and then spread the lie that he has been
raised from the dead.
So we are told that they stationed these
soldiers who would work on three-hour
shifts making sure that the tomb was not
disturbed. But when Jesus was raised
from the dead, these soldiers fell under
the power of God. They witnessed
it. And so the third witnesses to the
resurrection of Jesus were these women.
The Bible tells us these women was Mary
Magdalene, the other women and then Luke
24:10 as another woman by the name of
Joanna and other women as well. We don't
know how many they were. There were just
a whole company that came on Sunday
morning. As we said, they came to anoint
the body of Jesus according to Jewish
custom. As they came, they were going to
request
that the stone be removed so that they
could enter into the tomb to anoint the
body of Christ. What they didn't know
that is that before they came, the tomb
had been legally sealed by
Pilate. According to the requests of the
religious leaders, they said, "Not only
put guards there, but put a seal around
the stone so that if it's tempered with,
we can see that."
So the women come to the tomb and they
find the tomb
empty. And the religious leaders didn't
know what to do. And so the Bible tells
us when the women came into the tomb,
they were surprised at this. And this
was early in the morning and they made
their
way. Now how did this resurrection
happen? Because Paul is saying the same
power that raised Christ from the dead
is the same power that's working in your
life. The same power that raised Christ
from the dead is the same power that God
wants to work in your life this morning.
That same power. Well, we are told
number one there was an earthquake.
Matthew 16 to to verse two to verse 5 it
says very early in the next morning just
after sunrise they were on their way to
the tomb they asked each other who's
going to roll away the stone but when
they looked up they saw that the stone
which was there was very large and it
was rolled away now
note Bible historians tell us that the
religious leaders made sure that there
was a stone bigger than
others that would block the grave of
Jesus just to make sure nobody tempers
with it and if it is going to be removed
it's going to take a number of
people. So they were shocked when they
came this woman to think that this big
massive stone could be removed. But the
Bible tells us this big massive stone
was removed by a great by a great
earthquake. The Bible says behold there
was a great
earthquake. The word behold conveys the
emotion and the memory they had. The
word behold it means like Rachel. Wow.
They were shocked. They were
amazed. They were
bewildered. They were bewildered because
they couldn't imagine this stone being
moved by one person. For them, it was a
wild moment. For them, it was a moment
where they were stunned. They were
shocked. How did this happen? How was
the stone removed? Well, it was removed
by a great
earthquake. The word great means mega,
big, something massive, huge,
enormous. God sent a huge enormous
earthquake. God sent a massive
earthquake, a mega earthquake. That word
earthquake in Greek is the word
sismos which is the literal word of
earthquake. You all know that today we
are told about instruments that measure
or record the movement of the ground the
vibration of the earth called a
seismograph. It's just a small
instrument that is able to measure. What
does this mean? This means
this. It was the life of
God that moved away a stone that had
locked death on the
inside. When death comes, it takes God's
massive
earthquake to remove death and bring
about
life. The stone had sealed
death. The stone didn't want to allow
life to come. There are times in our
life when it's almost like we have been
shut in by
evil. Things are going on in your life
where you are going in circles and it
looks like you cannot break out of it.
You see it in your life. You see it in
your family. You see it in your
generation. You see it in your parents.
You see it in your in your own life. You
see it in your relative. It is like you
are in a grave.
And there's a big massive stone that has
shut you in. I'm here to tell somebody
that when the power of God comes upon
our lives, it becomes a wow moment.
When the power of resurrection life from
Jesus Christ comes, it becomes a moment
where God takes us out and extricates us
from a place of death.
When people look at you and they think
you'll never come out of that grave,
you'll never come out of that death. You
will never come out of that situation.
God looks and say I am going to
shine and God sends a sismograph called
resurrection
power. God intervenes in dead areas of
your life. He intervenes in your family.
He intervenes in your finances. He
intervenes in your spiritual life. God
gives you a new moment. I'm here to tell
you we are celebrating a new moment
today because of what God does in our
[Applause]
lives. Even if there are large spiritual
rocks that are blocking your
success, rocks that seal try to seal
death. Rocks that will not allow your
life to come into a new season. But
God's resurrection
power removes those rocks through the s
seismic activity of God's
intervention. God sends a heavenly
earthquake called the chyros moment.
Note this very interesting that the
seismic activity that happened the
earthquake that happened did not destroy
the other
infrastructure. It only destroyed the
hindrances that were at the grave to
usher in newness of life and bring life
and freedom.
You see, when God initiates
earthquakes, he only deals with a
problem and leaves every other
thing. The first earthquake we are
reading about is about this one when
Jesus was raised from the
dead. But we read about another
earthquake in Acts 4:31.
The Bible tells us that as the believers
were
gathered, as they were
praying, there was an
earthquake. And the Bible says they were
filled with the Holy Spirit and they
spoke the word with
boldness. You see, prayer brings us into
a season of divine earthquakes.
When we come before God in prayer, when
we call to God in prayer, when we turn
to God in prayer, God brings in our
lives a season of
earthquakes. And that's why prayer
changes things. That's why when you
start praying, things begin to change in
your life. That's why some of you things
have begun to change in your life. Ever
since you turned to God, God is sending
earthquakes. God is telling those stones
that are trying to block your success,
this is my daughter. This is my son.
This is my servant. You can't stop them.
Can I hear an amen in this place? This
is my daughter. This is my son. You
can't stop them. But interesting, we
read about another earthquake, the third
one in Acts chapter 16.
Paul and Silas were preaching in the
city of Philippi in
Macedonia and they encountered a young
woman
there who was a fortune teller.
She followed Paul and Silas for several
days.
And several days later, Paul realized
that what this woman was saying to them,
she was saying it by the power of
demonic spirits that were in her. So
Paul turns to this
girl, commands the demons to come out of
her, and these spirits come out of her.
What they didn't know is was that this
young lady was bringing in a lot of
money through fortune telling and
working for the
masters. And when Paul exercised the
demons out of her, she couldn't do this
fortuneelling business
anymore. And the masters noticing that
their business was
affected, they rose up against Paul and
Silas.
They brought them before the
magistrates. Somehow Paul and Silas were
found
guilty. They were
charged. They were taken and scourged on
the back, bound with
chains, thrown into
prison, and locked behind
bars. And just to make sure they don't
escape, they posted a soldier
there who guarded the prison door around
the clock 24/7. They would work in
3-hour
shifts. Very
interesting. Here's Paul and
Silas. They are in
jail. Their backs are bleeding. They are
in chains. They are falsely accused.
Instead of
them feeling sorry for
themselves, the Bible says at
midnight, Paul and Silas
prayed and sent praises to
God. At
midnight, you know, I was talking to one
of the doctors in a church and he told
us a very interesting story. He said,
you know, in in medical science, they
know
that people the majority of people die
at
night. People die at
night. And if you've ever been ill, I
don't know how many of you have ever
been ill or if you have a tooth ache,
how many of you know that you can go
around the whole day dancing and
shouting ma at night?
You can't
sleep. Somehow it looks like all the
pain and the sorrow comes at
night. Have you ever injured yourself,
bumped your leg against something and
you just shook it off during the day?
You are all okay and you went to bed,
but then midnight
came and all of a sudden you were up.
Which means at the height of their
pain, Paul and Silas
decided, instead of focusing on our
pain, we're going to pray. We're going
to sing praises to God. Oh, hallelujah.
Do we have people who do that? Instead
of looking at your pain and looking at
your sorrow, you're going to pray.
You're going to sing praises to
God. And just to make sure they were not
whispering, the Bible says, "And the
other prisoners heard
them. No, they were not praying under
their breath." Uh-uh. They were real
Pentecostal charismatic. They were
making noise. They were shouting
everywhere. Do we have people who know
how to shout to the Lord in this place
and praise him and thank him?
But it's interesting that it says at
midnight. We are told that the darkest
time of the day is
midnight. That's when it's
darkest. That's when darkness is at its
peak. However, just few seconds after
midnight is the coming in of a new day.
Masalon, some of you, you may be at the
midnight of your life
today, but I'm here to tell you that if
you were to sing praises to God, if you
were to pray to God, God is going to
send a heavenly earthquake that's going
to shake everything in your
life. They send praises to God. Let me
read the rest of the story. It says
about midnight Paul and Silas were
praying and singing hymns to God and the
rest of the prisoners were listening to
them. Suddenly, somebody say
suddenly tell your neighbors suddenly.
Tell your other neighbors
suddenly. La neighbors alone. Please
listen. There are times when you do what
God tells you and it looks like it
doesn't work.
Some of you, you may have been committed
to doing what's right, praying, singing,
reading God's word, doing whatever, but
it looks like it's not
working. But I want to tell
you, your prayers are not in
vain. Your worship is not in
vain. Your service to God is not in
vain. God is going to send his heavenly
suddenly. You see, when breakthroughs
comes, it's a type of a heavenly
earthquake. And when breakthrough comes,
they only deal with a problem and they
focus on the
problem. And God's going to give
somebody some suddenly here today in the
name of Jesus. Tell your neighbor, your
suddenly are is coming. your suddenly
are coming. Tell them little duba, your
suddenly are
coming. Secondly, the verse says, "And
behold, there was a great earthquake."
Somebody say,
"Behold." Say it
again. Say it
again. Look at your neighbor and say,
"Never
behold." Tell them again. Never behold.
Tell them again, neighbor,
behold. Know this, when the earthquake
hit, the large stone that was sealed was
dislodged and rolled away by the enemy.
In other words, death that was sealed
away, death that was supposed to be
permanent, death that was supposed to
incapacitate
Jesus, death that was supposed to be the
destiny of our Lord. All of a sudden,
that death was invaded by the lifegiving
presence of God.
In other words, when
God brings about resurrection
life, he will perform some
beholds in your
life. The word behold means
see,
look,
observe. It means take notice. You're
going to see something different.
My late
father
who was raised in
Mambid, he used to tell me a story as I
was growing up as a child that in the
village where he was raised, they they
had a lot of animals and a lot of
birds. And he told me as a child that
there was this particular
bed that if it sat next to a specific
house and started chirping in a certain
way, you knew that
something was coming to that house.
Unfortunately, it was like someone in
that home would die. But I want to take
that story and turn it around.
He said this bird when it
chapped it sounded like it was
saying tell your
neighbor for those of you who don't
understand this heavenly language it
means tomorrow you will
see it means you tomorrow you will
behold
something. God has a way of bringing
those
seasons. God is telling people, don't
discard this, my child. Don't write
their obituary. Don't tell them that
they will never come back.
God has a way of bringing your situation
of a sealed grave back to life. God has
a way of coming into a dead situation
and bringing life into that death
situation.
Now Isaiah stands up and speaks by the
Holy
Spirit and talks to a people who are
discouraged, to a people who think
nothing's going to change. To a people
who think they are destiny of evil is
sealed forever. And he stands up by the
spirit and he speaks to them by the
spirit. And he is speaking to you today.
And this is what he says. By the
inspiration of God, God says,
"Behold, I will do a new
thing." Ah, you didn't hear me. God
says, "I will do a new
thing." I will do. I will
do. I will take the initiative. I will
take the first step. You don't have to
wait for anything. I will take the first
step. God says, I will take the first
step even if you think you don't deserve
it. I will take the first step. Even if
you think you are sinful, I will take
the first step even if you think you are
not in my line. I will take the first
step.
Behold, behold, I will do a new thing.
He says, "Now it shall spring
forth. Shall you not know
it? I will even make a road in the
wilderness and rivers in the desert."
This is somebody's word today. God is
going to do what you have never expected
before. God's going to give you a behold
in your life.
In the New Living Translation, it means
for I'm about to do something
new. See, I've already begun. Do you not
see it? I'll make a pathway through the
wilderness. I will create rivers in the
desert. God does
suddenly. I said God does suddenly.
It says
suddenly and he sense an earthquake and
finally when the women came to the tomb,
the Bible says they were
bewildered. They were
shocked. Luke 24 says they were
perplexed. Why? Because they found the
stone rolled away.
They were so perplexed that they bowed
their faces to the
ground. They were blown
away. Now consider the following
things. We said that the stone was a big
one, too large to be removed by a human.
Too enormous in
size for any human being to remove it.
The authorities had made sure it is
sealed.
They had made sure they put a guard
there. They didn't want Jesus to come
out of the grave at
all. You see, there are times when Satan
wants you to believe you'll never come
out of your situation.
But you must look at him and
say weeping may endure for a
night. At midnight I'm going to sing
praises to God and at midnight God's
going to send his earthquake.
The Bible tells us that when the angel
removed the stone, the soldiers ran
away. So when the women came there, that
which was preventing everything, the
stone, the guard, the seal, it wasn't
there anymore
because it doesn't matter what they used
to do in your
life. It doesn't matter what they said.
It doesn't matter what they prophesied.
It doesn't matter what hle they place.
It doesn't matter if they scheme against
you. It doesn't matter if they plan
against you. It doesn't matter if they
ostracize
you. He moves everything aside.
And when all this
happened and the women got into the
tomb, the angel answered and said to
them, "Fear
not. I know you're looking for Jesus who
was crucified, he is not
here. He is risen." And and what the
angel says, "Come and
see the
place where your Lord
lay." That expression come and see is
the same as the word
behold,
perceive,
scrutinize, look with intent.
It means examine, have a full view,
experience. It
means I don't want you to get it from
other people. I want you to see it with
your own eyes. I want you to have a
personal testimony yourself.
God says, "I don't want you to hear
about other people's miracles. I I want
you to get your own miracle. I don't
want you to hear the stories of other
people. You will have your own story.
Can I hear an amen in the house?" You
will have your own
story. You will have your own story of
the God interventions in your life. You
will have your own story of the of the
intervention of God in your life. You
will have your own story of the chyros
moment in your life. You will have your
own story of the divine earthquakes in
your life. You will have your own
story. You will have your own
story. The angel says come and see. So
that when you tell others, you don't
tell them the story of others.
You tell them, "My life was locked in
death, but God broke the
seal. God rolled the stone away." And
the stone was not a small one. It was a
mega stone. It was a big stone. It
wasn't just small problems. It was big
problems. It was things that I didn't
know how I am going to solve. But God
intervened in my life.
I saw what God can
do with my own
eyes. God is inviting
you to be an
eyewitness of what he can
do. God is inviting
you to have a
firsthand
encounter. Some of you, you came, you've
been invited.
You look at your life
and it's like you are in a grave
yourself. Everything around smells of
death. Nothing
working, nothing
moving. It's a place of
stagnation, nothing
new. But you are here
today. Here on resurrection
day, here on Sunday
morning, you've gathered with us
today to lift up your hands to
God, to pray and sing praises to
God, but even more
so to say,
God, here's my
life. Satan wanted me to believe
that things will remain as they
are. He put a big stone, sealed it,
guarded
it. But I've heard
you can bring newness of life in my
life. Some of
you, you've walked away from
God. Even though you love God, you go to
church, but you haven't given your life
to
Christ. And you look at your life and
you see everything falling
apart. But God has given you another
chance. It's a new morning. It's a new
day. It's resurrection day.
Will you take a step towards
Christ? Receive him in your life as your
savior and your
lord and you will see for
yourself what God can do in your life.
Let's bow our heads and pray together.
[Music]
choy.
could more
and
come good.
Give it.
[Music]
that that that's you. You're saying,
"God, I've I've heard your word. I'm not
going to sit back in my seat and not
respond. I'm not going to sit back in my
grave and allow my death and allow my
life to rot and
die. I want to take a step. I want to
invite you Jesus to come into my heart
and be my savior and my lord. Our heads
bowed, our eyes closed. If that is
you and you say, "Today, I want to
invite Jesus into my life. I want Jesus
to come into my heart and be the savior
and the lord of my life. I need prayer."
If that is you, right where you are, if
you need prayer, would you please just
raise your hand right where you are?
Just raise it up. I want to pray for
you. Raise it high. I want to pray for
you. This is your day. Don't postpone.
Don't say no. This is your day. This is
your time. God wants to do something in
your life. This is resurrection day.
Resurrection life is right here. Raise
that
hand. Thank you for those hands. God
bless you all. I want to ask you to do
one more thing. If you raised your hand,
I want to pray for you. Would you please
stand on your feet right where you are?
Please, if you raised your head, kindly,
please just stand on your feet. That's
right. All over the stadium. All over.
All over. Come on. All over the stadium.
That's right. That's right. That's
right. I want I'm going to ask you to do
one more thing. I'm going to ask you
take all your belongings, your Bible,
your bag, your purse, whatever you have,
and come from where you are and come to
the front. I want to pray for you. Even
those of you who are at the very top, we
will wait for you. Come on. Come, come,
let's pray together. Come, let's pray
together. Come
on. Come
[Music]
on. Give them a big hand.
Everybody.
Listen what they are saying. They are
saying this. Come on.
Keep on walking.
Give
it to
me. Come on. Keep on rocking. Keep on
rocking.
[Applause]
How good is
he? Give it.
That's right. Shall we all stand on our
feet? Everybody please. Shall we all
stand on our feet as we
I've got
[Music]
Oh,
you will
be
Give
me give
it
your
heart.
How could you feel?
[Music]
Let's give these people a big hand as
they're walking to the front. Everybody,
I come on and understand. Aren't you
glad that God is changing somebody's
life? Aren't you glad that God is
changing somebody's life here?
Thank you
[Music]
Lord. Thank you
Lord. Give them a big hand please.
[Music]
We
are heaven.
is in
Sh.
[Music]
He will come
He will
come
down. He's
over.
He's
over. He's
[Music]
is awesome.
Let's give our Lord a big hand and thank
him for this great harvest of souls.
[Music]
Seeking
ch. Oh
yeah. Oh yeah.
[Music]
Now I
go
[Music]
sh. All right. I just want to say to
every one of
you, I'm really
really I can tell you how to put it. My
heart is moved to the
core
because only God can take a
life
that's like in a
grave and change it.
Let them help you
lady. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Is uncomfortable. Yeah.
Even don't. Yeah. Sorry. Nana.
Sorry.
Sorry. Just help her please. So
much. All right.
You know, people don't understand how
much God loves
them and they don't understand what God
can do when you see the little ones
running to the front like that one over
there. That's a good one over there just
running to the front. My goodness me.
Jesus.
Wow.
[Music]
Wow. Thank you,
Lord. Join me in prayer, please. You can
remain standing. Just raise your hands
to the
Lord. Pray with me. Heavenly Father,
[Music]
today I give my life to
you. I invite Jesus
Christ to come into my
heart to be the savior.
and the Lord of my
life. Let the resurrection
life come into my life
today and take me out of prison.
Take me out of the
[Music]
grave of
evil, bad
luck,
curses,
misfortune. Let new
life come in my life
today that I may know you,
Jesus, as my
savior. and let a new
season begin in my
life because of your work in my
life. I thank you for hearing my
prayer. I thank you for coming into my
heart in Jesus name.
Amen.
Amen and amen. Praise the Lord.
I'm going to ask you, we want to talk to
you just for a few minutes.
Please to your left. That way, please to
your left
and just follow them. We want to talk to
you for a few minutes and quickly come
back. All right? Because we have another
service coming. All right? Let's just
let's just follow those people. Then
you'll come back quickly. Give them a
big hand as they go, please. God bless.
[Music]
Come on.
[Applause]
It's
again
now in Jesus
My god is
[Music]
quality.
Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
[Music]
Who
are all
[Applause]
Where my
[Music]
Hey, when I'm No
way. Heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Jesus. I
[Applause]
jump. When the
world will
Heat.
Yeah.
Yeah. Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah. Please, please remain
standing as we welcome our speaker
today. He was born again on the 6th of
June
1978. Entered into full-time ministry in
1980 as pastor in the montaneous kingdom
of Guauqua. After which in 1987 he
launched the prestigious Gospel Fire
Evangelistic Ministries International.
He's married to Emily and together they
share four wonderful children. He
received his theological training from
the international theological
institution. He holds a BA honors in
theology from the University of Portrom.
His ministry has been a great success
and has brought forth many outstanding
church leaders and pastors. His bold and
imaginative ways are prove of that
indeed he was raised by God for times
such as this. He has a deep dedication
to his vision which makes him one of the
leading evangelists not only in South
Africa but also worldwide as he has
traveled to nations around Africa, USA,
Asia, Europe and the Middle East from
1987. He has preached tirelessly and has
shared his vision
unselfishly reaching millions in the
past 10 years. His preaching is not
based on the persuasive speech of human
wisdom, but on the demonstration of the
spirit and power and the Holy Spirit
giving testimony to his word by signs
and miracles of every kind. It's my
great honor bayou and my greatest
pleasure to invite on stage Reverend
Prophet
Evangelist Ta Ra
[Music]
Thank you
Jesus.
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah. I say
hallelujah. Oh, thank you Jesus. Thank
you Jesus. Thank you
Jesus. What a wonderful day today.
In this great
day of remembering our Lord Jesus
Christ when he
kicked the power of death from the
grave and the stone roll
away and he declare I was dead but now
I'm alive forever more.
My greetings to our great
bishop, Bishop
Mosaso
meo, our mother in this great ministry,
Grace Bible
Church that I had a privilege of knowing
the ministry over 30 to 40
years and also the privilege of being
invited in some of the meetings. I tell
not do not take it for
granted all the servants of the Lord who
are here supporting and those the the
local pastors leaders and and the the
people around and uh the the community
of Souetu and Kening who have gathered
to to celebrate with this with us in
this conference. I greet you in the big
in the wonderful name of our Lord Jesus
Christ. Say amen.
I really I'm really touched
tonight to be part of this
2025 day on
Sunday of resurrection.
I know that the whole country was
praying. I've seen people walking into
services in an amazing
way. And I believe deep down in my heart
that we are on the
threshold of a mighty revival that is
going to sweep this country.
It's not starting now but it is looming
on the atmosphere. It's like you can
raise your hands on touch what God is
doing on the
atmosphere. In few minutes in few months
I have seen miracles happening all over
this country that I thought those things
will never happen in our lifetime
anymore.
And I want to thank the Lord
today to witness the power of
God. And I thank what God is doing here
in
Suetto. seeing on Sunday morning
thousands and thousands of people
gathering to hear the same old story of
Jesus Christ who died on the cross who
went to the grave for three days and
three nights and risen from the dead.
That old story it is our power even
today to resurrect our lives.
We don't get tired to talk about this
story. Many stories uh many historians
uh have fabricated things and they came
and disappeared. But the story of Jesus
Christ, the Jesus who was born, who was
registered at home affairs, who walk
upon this planet, who suffer as a human
being, but he he died on the cross of
Calvary, who went to the grave like you
and I, but on the third day, he rose
from the dead. I'm declaring tonight,
he's alive.
[Applause]
I am going to
read a very simple
scripture and I'm I was happy just to
hear the portion of the bishop's
message. I was so tempted to say bishop
square. But thank you men of God. Thank
you for trusting me for such a great
responsibility of sharing the word in
your church. And uh my message is not
going to be a long message because you
know what will you say after the bishop
has preached. I always say I always
think must give me to preach first so
that the bishop will come and
[Music]
say but I want to thank you for honoring
me so much. Turn with me to the book of
Acts or let me put it in very well very
in a South African. The book of
Acts. So I was I thought I was in in
Nigeria. The book of
acts chapter number
two verse 22 I will read few
verses and I'm going to travel like a
how rain there's no robot for how
rain may verse number 22
Men of
Israel, listen to
this. Jesus of
Nazareth was a
man accredited by
God to you by
miracles, wonders, and
signs which God did among you through
him. As you yourself
know, this man was handed over to you by
God's purpose. Set purpose. Everybody
say set
purpose. Everybody say set
purpose.
And for
knowledge. Everybody say for
knowledge. Those mark those two things.
This is the God we are talking
about. Crucifixion of Jesus Christ was
not an accident to
God. Crucif and the death of Jesus was
not accidental.
There
is there is a
set
purpose. There
is a
for
knowledge. The devil is a
liar. The devil is a liar.
This was something
set by
God. And you with a wicked man, wicked
hands, you put him by nailing him to the
cross.
But God raised him from the dead,
freeing him from the agony of death
because it was impossible.
It was impossible for death to keep him
its hold on him. Glory.
Glory. Father, I thank you for the
moment you give me to share the word of
God. Open our eyes
again to understand the
mysterious
ways that you have done to bring
salvation of men to us in Jesus. Amen.
The message on this
book I
think it
is
postresurrection
message which also
embrace the baptism of the Holy Spirit.
spirit because the baptism of the Holy
Spirit came to explain more the
resurrection, the death and the
resurrection of Jesus more than anything
else in this world.
Peter after he received the spirit like
other 120 people, he stood up to explain
the
phenomena. He said in his speech, "Men
of Israel, I'm here to explain what I
was afraid to explain before I received
the Holy Spirit." Listen to me. You
cannot be able to understand uh the
death and the resurrection of Jesus
unless you have the spirit of
God because it was a
mystery to the enemy, the mystery to the
devil. It is something that was hidden
in God before the beginning.
Now, Peter was used by the Holy Spirit
to explain what
happened. He's addressing the people of
Israel who were supposed to know better
than other
people. What happened on the
cross? It is after some months, after
some days. But now the Holy Spirit is
coming to explain the phenomena, the
thing that happened on the cross, the
thing that happened on the resurrection
day. He said, I want you to know first
of
all
that whatever happened on
Friday, it was not an accident. I want
to repeat it again.
The death of Jesus Christ was not an
accident. It was not car head on
collusion on the freeway. My God, it was
not an accident. The Bible says, The
Bible says it happened according to the
set purpose. When the Bible speaks about
a set purpose, it means that God when he
set a purpose, no one can change it. A
set purpose is not subject to any
prophet. A set purpose it will happen
according to the will of God. We are
here about the set purpose of of God.
Nobody will change what God is doing in
this world. Is it a set
purpose? And number two, because the
devil did not know. It says and the full
knowledge of God. Meaning that God was
not surprised by anything on the cross
of Calvary because of two things. It was
a set purpose and it was a full
knowledge of God. God knew the details.
He knew the pains that the son of God
will go through. He knew the graves. He
knew the power of the
grave. Peter was preaching to the
people. But listen to
me.
Fore when he could not be he could not
be
recognized when he was hanging there.
Messiah. But the priest, the chief
priest and the priest and the scribes
and the elders of the church were
shaking their head and say, "If you are
the son of God, come down. We will
believe in you." Have you realized that
people want to believe you when you come
down?
How
about come down we'll believe in you and
those who are religious world be careful
of the religious world that does not
know
Jesus and they they prophesy sometimes
you
know you trusted God let him release you
from your pain. I said, "Good shot. You
will see that God will never forget
those who trust in him." That's why
David says, "Though I walk in the valley
of the shadow of death, I shall fear no
evil because the Lord is with me. He
prepares a table in the midst of my
enemies. Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life. I
will dwell in the house of for the Lord
forever."
There's a table after
crucifixion. There's a table after the
shadow of death. There's a table after a
life-threatening situation. There's a
table after the people have mocked you.
There's a table after the wounds upon
your shoulder. There's a table after you
have cried on the cross. There's a table
after your trouble sitting here in the
stadium. You have gone through certain
stuff. But I'm here to encourage you
that there is a table uh that is
prepared for you uh after you have
finished the cause after the trouble are
over and God does not want to bless you.
He want to gather your
enemies so that they can see how God
bless those that the world said he they
will not be blessed.
You know sometimes God delay to bless us
because he want to gather closer our
enemies so that our enemies should come
and see when we celebrate what they
thought we'll never
celebrate. Maybe your miracle have
delayed but Lord did not want to heal
you there. He wanted to heal you in this
stadium so that he can glorify himself
in this Passover.
[Applause]
The enemy Satan did not know the setup.
That's why Satan has been blundering. I
believe certain if we can take him to
Steve B hospital or Barakonath they will
diagnose him that he is psychopath maybe
schizophrenia because the god has been
playing with the mind of this guy he's
no more well we are just we are just
dealing with somebody who is a mental
face. God has said some things that
nobody can
change. Let me tell you in your life
there are things that God has said. The
devil will come with storms but he
cannot change because there's a setup.
It's a setup. God put you in that
position. The devil think that you are
dying. You are not dying. It's a set up.
The devil think you are on the cross
bleeding. No, he doesn't know that God
is setting you up and he's about to show
up today. When the devil saw Jesus
bleeding, he thought is a time for hell
to celebrate. He did not know the death
of Jesus was a setup.
Unfortunately, the devil doesn't have
advices and let me tell
you he has he has done it with a
fornowledge. God knows
everything about my life and your life.
Everything everything. If I was
preaching in in up in Africa, I was
everything. He knows
everything that you are going
through. God knows
everything. God knows everything.
God has already prepared something
better than what you are crying for
because he knows everything about your
life. That's why when they complain
about the stone, God has already
prepared that the stone shall roll
away. He didn't needed human assistance
in resurrection.
God wanted to be
alone with Lazarus. He asked them to
help. But for his son, he didn't need
human
assistance. They found an angel sitting
on top of the of on top of the stone.
[Music]
Nobody can remove God because your
problem
He's sitting on top of your trouble
today and nobody can remove it.
[Applause]
The Bible
says you crucified him with your hands.
But but
God but God.
[Music]
Today have tried
everything but God has a plan for your
life which will never be shaken by
anybody. It is
amazing. The writer of the Bible, many
believe, is Luke who wrote the book of
Acts. He said, "You did it by the hands
of the
wicked,
but
God lose him from death."
Everybody say, "But
God." But
God, it doesn't matter how t how
terrible and how how how how painful was
the death of Jesus on the cross. It
doesn't matter how tight was the grave
that was got even by soldiers.
But bad God.
but
God. But
God, but
God, your doctors told you that you'll
never survive for 6 months, but God says
today you are healed in the name of
Jesus
Christ. Yeah.
Your neighbor said that you are so
stupid that you cannot even manage to do
that good work that you have received. I
said but
God some they told you that you are born
from a family that has a chaos and
therefore you cannot achieve anything in
this world because your mother was
cursed. They say your father was a drunk
so you cannot be a sober child. I say
yes. My father was a drunker but
God. But
God. Whatever the people has decided is
not final. It might be a fact but it's
not final.
God comes when people has decided that
you will never make it and say I will
come when people said it will never
happen I will come and make
[Music]
it that's why
Peter Peter said something that really
touched me these few days he
said, "But God raised him from the
dead
because it was
impossible for death to keep him hold on
him." Okay. Look to your person and say,
"Neighbor, it was
impossible. I can't keep her in that
thing.
It was
impossible that today I can still be
under the control of the power of death
is impossible. I'm here to declare that
Orlando stadium whatever the devil have
said about your life about your future
about your children is
impossible. It is
impossible cuz God has already set a
stage for your life. God has already
sought out your destiny before you were
born. God has a fornowledge about you
and God knows
everything. He has predestined you to be
a child of God by his word. It's
impossible. is impossible to the devil
to bring you down. When you go through a
shadow, tell the devil, it's impossible
to bring down to me. Bring me down after
I have seen such a great power. It's
impossible to bring me down. After I
have seen such great miracles, after I
have seen this Jesus who was
accredited, he was not one of the people
who are doing miracles without
accreditation. He was
accredited. He was a given
recognition that
you you have a right. you
qualify that you can walk upon the Sea
of
Galilee after this great thing. It's
impossible for the devil to grab us back
to death. I'm telling the devil now,
Satan, it is
impossible. They are too great. It's
impossible that we can backslide and go
back. Is
impossible. Such a great resurrection of
Jesus Christ from the dead. It is
impossible. It is
impossible that we can go
back. There's a song that we used to
sing. When I remember the things that
the Lord has
done, it's
impossible. Impossible.
I have not come here Satan to forget
what the Lord has done in my life. Is
impossible when I remember where you
found me. Is impossible to go back to
the things of the devil again. Even
those who were tired this holidays some
some people were sitting tired and
thinking I'm going back. They were
trying coming to try for the last time.
I'm here to tell you it is impossible
for you to backslide after such a great
thing that the Lord has done in your
life. It is
impossible. What makes Peter to say
that? Peter
said what makes it impossible is
this. Oh my god. What makes this to be
possible is
this. You know,
Bishop, I was laughing.
[Music]
When Jesus was in the
cross, it's
impossible. That's why I was
amazed because the Bible says here, the
Bible says here when he was there on the
[Applause]
cross, it was impossible for death to
keep him hold for David
said, "You don't know know what you are
hearing from this stadium. You don't
know how many the journey that you are
going to walk start from this place
where you are. The things that you are
hearing is not the things that you just
entertain your soul. But God is speaking
the food for the journey. You are taking
vituals. Some of the things that are
said here, you will understand after 20
years that if there was no revival in
Orlando stadium on that morning uh of
resurrection, I could not have been
standing where I'm standing today. Uh
but the psalm that David did when he was
in the backside of the desert, he was
composing alone. But that psalm was
going to help Jesus when he was in the
graveuh and the grave was shut up and
the stench of death was beginning to
come out. But when he was inside Peter,
he said it was
impossible. Why it was
impossible is
because David said
can work sometimes.
[Music]
David says there are many Davids here in
this place. We have our
[Music]
David. Rest in peace.
I don't write don't don't write don't
write
ri some of you you don't even know
what's is
rip return if
[Applause]
possible
inulos lunal laa
He
is
not
[Music]
here. When I was in Israel, they said,
"I must go and check the tomb of Jesus."
I look I look at it from a distance. I
saw no there's something built on top of
that mo that that grave and it's written
in
Arabic. God has got no
son. I said no I'm not going. You know
what? Why I'm not going to check?
Because I know what will I find there.
He
is not here. Where is Jesus? As I'm
speaking now, he's in Soeteru in Orlando
stadium. What he's doing in Orlando? He
has come to deliver people from the
grave of sin. He's coming to deliver
people from the power of the devil. He's
coming to heal the sick. He's coming to
open the blind eyes. He's coming to open
the deaf ears. He's coming to get to to
to get those who are crippled to rise up
and walk in the name of Jesus. I say
Jesus is here this morning. Uh he's not
in the grave. Uh he's here this morning.
Uh he's alive forever and ever. He's
ready to enter your heart. He's ready to
save you from the wrecket life. He's
ready to save you from the power of
Satan. He's ready to deliver you from a
demonic power. He is
here. It's
impossible. It's
impossible. This is what kept him. David
said, David
said, "I saw the Lord always before
me." It was a
psalm. I saw the Lord always before
me. I see him always before me. Even
when the dark becomes darker, I see him
always before me. Even when I don't feel
him, but I saw him before me every day
of my life. When Jesus was on the cross,
uh when he said, "Why hast thou forsaken
me?" He remember the psalm of David uh
that says uh I saw the Lord uh always
before me. Even when I feel like I'm
abandoned even I feel that I'm rejected
uh I see the Lord always before me. Even
in the body that is bleeding uh even in
the body that is bitten uh beyond
recognition.
But I see the Lord always before
[Music]
me. And he
says because he is at my right
hand. And he say I will not be
shaken. Death will never shake me. Satan
will never shake me.
Modernism will never shake me. Things
that are will never shake me. That
things that are proclaimed are being
proclaimed that are coming will never
shake me. Those prophets who are saying
uh that the church will never survive
the next 3 years, I say it doesn't shake
me. Uh the people that says there is no
more true men of God in South Africa, it
doesn't shake me. The people that says
uh the church is dying uh I say you are
a liar. You don't shake me. Uh because
uh the Lord is always before me. Uh and
I shall not be shaken uh by anything. Uh
I shall be not shaken by Satanism. Uh I
shall not be shaken by witchcraft. I
shall not be shaken uh by sicknesses uh
and disease that are coming uh one by
one upon the planet earth. I shall not
be shaken because I'm here by the set
[Applause]
purpose. I shall not be
[Music]
shaken.
Therefore, my heart is glad and my
tongue
rejoices. My body also will live in
hope. When Jesus was attacked in until
the grave, he prophesy. He repeated the
word of his grandfather. He says, "My
body is wounded. My body has got no
shape anymore, but I'm going to rest in
hope." I want to tell my followers that
I will rest in hope. I will never rest
miserably. What does it mean to rest in
hope? It means
that weepings only last for a night. But
joy comes in the morning. It's only
Friday. Uh Saturday is coming.
only Saturday of silence when the Bible
did not talk about Jesus but Jesus was
going down to the lowest parts of the
blinded earth. He was visiting the
prison uh that was under the world
telling them the good news uh that you
see me here. My body's in the grave but
my soul is in God. But I'm here to tell
you the good news that salvation is
guaranteed. Salvation is guaranteed that
men can be set free. Men can be free
from the power of the devil and the
demons. Men can be free from the
witchcraft. You can be free from sin and
[Music]
Satan.
For you
have made known the me to known to me
the path of life. You will fill me with
joy in your presence.
Mama, this
person is dying or he's dead. But
David's
words raise him because there was hope
that I will leave. I will rest in hope.
I will never rest and never come back.
I'll rest in hope knowing on the third
day my father will say when the the seat
of justice is
satisfied by the
witnesses I shall
arise and say I was dead but I am alive
now forever more I have the key of of
death and hide
[Music]
The Lord said to my Lord,
about your
life. The Lord
said to my Lord,
[Music]
Sit at my right hand until I make your
enemies
foottool under your
[Music]
feet. As we are living
today, God is
busy with your
enemy to bring
them under your feet.
is not you fighting this battle
now. God is busy preparing them under
your
feet. Sit. Don't panic. Sit. Don't go up
and down and change churches like you
change socks. Sit. Don't be found here
and found there tomorrow. Sit. Don't
change pastors like you change
BMWs.
Sit.
Sit. Sit. If there are enemies where you
are,
sit. He will bring your enemies under
your feet. Sit.
Some are facing discipline
M7. I say to you, don't go to the
sanas sit. I will make your enemies a
foot stool under your feet. It's not
your job to
use. It's not your your job to use.
[Music]
Hey, sit. God will put your enemies
under your
[Applause]
[Music]
They are alive because
[Applause]
what they said will never happen in your
life. That's why they are alive. That's
why Jesus said, God said, "Sit on my
right hand until I bring your enemies
under your feet."
Those who are against you, they have to
have long life. Uh so that they can see
uh when the Lord bless you in the open,
when they see what they said will never
happen, it must happen in the presence
of your enemies.
Ma,
mother the time.
those who are talking about you say
you'll never rise up. You'll never make
it in
life as I'm talking right now because
they are about to see you sitting down.
They are about to feed you and they will
see you not in the grave anymore but
they will see you sitting next to Jesus
after resurrection. God is not afraid to
raise you from the dead just to go to
Kentucky chicken with
you. There was no reason to raise
Lazarus except he was raised to sit with
Jesus and eat that supper only. And we
and Lazarus disappeared in the
Bible. And be safe
today. Why do you get saved? I don't
want to promise you that when you get
saved, you'll get a doublestory
house. That gospel, you'll find it
somewhere else. But today I say if you
receive Jesus today, one day you shall
sit next to Jesus in the kingdom of a
father. God and God are speaking about
you right now. There is discussion about
your life. There is discussion about the
things that you are going through right
now. God is telling God, "Leave this
enemy. I'm about to make them something.
I will make them the foottool."
25 to fight with
you. And when I don't kick them, just
feed them whatever fall from the
master's
table. Sure.
with sit on my right hand. You will
see in every situation
[Music]
but
God but but God I don't
know situation as well I want to talk to
your situation right now it's terrible
yes it has been declared you have a
letter that tells you about all the
things that scare you but I say but God
has a purpose that set for your
[Music]
life. Let them look around. You are
still alive because God has a purpose
for your life. As I'm talking right now,
everybody who's who's sick on the body
in this in this stadium, I am standing
here as a prophet of God. I declare and
I decree in the mighty name of Jesus, be
healed wherever you are. Be free. Be
healed. It might be kidneys. It might be
sugar diabetes. Uh it might be high
blood pressure. It might be fracture on
your bone. It might be it might be
headache, migraine. I command migraine,
headache to be healed in the name of
Jesus Christ. I command the blindness to
open. Uh it might be deaf ears. Uh I
command the deaf ears to be opened. Uh
in the name of Jesus, I command those
who are holding crushes and wheelchairs
who cannot walk. I command you, you were
told by the hospital that you will walk
until you die. But I declare in the name
of Jesus, rise up and be healed in the
mighty name of Jesus. Uh, let your ear
be unstopped right now in the name of
Jesus. Let your tongue be strengthened
and you begin to talk right now in the
mighty name of Jesus. Let your knees be
strengthened and you start to jump right
now in the mighty name of Jesus. Let
your shift hand be strengthened right
now and be healed in the name of Jesus.
like a woman who was bent down. I
command you spirit of infirmity, leave
that woman and woman thou art loose in
Jesus mighty name. Uh to that father I
say father your broken back from the
accident I say may your let your bones
come together and be strengthened and
you walk like a young man now in the
name of Jesus. Give God a hand of praise
if you can.
[Music]
[Applause]
Shake your body and check where is the
disease. Check the body and check where
is the pain. By his prayer, by his
stripes, we were healed. Check. Check
yourself. Check yourself. Where's the
pain? Where's the pain? Where? It's
gone. It's gone in the name of Jesus.
It's gone in the name of Jesus. It's
gone. The pain is gone in the name of
Jesus. The pain is gone. The demonic
power is gone. The one who came here
with with demons that were speaking to
his head. I command you right now, those
evil voices are gone in the name of
Jesus. those who have come here with a
with a spiritual husband or a spiritual
wife. I don't know what's that but I
need to preach about it because some
have spiritual wife. I command that
spiritual wife to go back to where he
come from and he set you
free. I command that ticki to go back to
the place it belong in Jesus mighty
name.
Breast
cancer. Breast
cancer die in the name of Jesus from
that
person. I know. I know it's it's dying
right now. Right now. In the name of
Jesus. Breast cancer die is dead in the
name of Jesus. You can touch your
breast. You are free in Jesus mighty
name. your neck problem. If you are
covering your neck with a bracelet, you
can take it off right now and begin to
enjoy life like everybody. If you walk
with sticks, put it next to you and
start to stretch your your legs and
enjoy healing because uh he was
resurrected so that our body must be
resurrected from every sickness.
[Music]
Yes, it's happening. It's happening
somewhere. It's happening. It's
happening. Some are getting healed. Some
are getting free in Jesus name. Some
demonic spirit are getting out of people
in Jesus name. Somebody who could not
hear. Your ears are hearing now. Hearing
the sound of the sound now the sound.
You can hear the sound. Clap your hands
and praise them. You can hear right
[Music]
now. Somebody could not stand. Just
stand up and sit down and check
yourself. Check what the Lord has done.
But God, you were told that you cannot
enjoy that anymore. I say but God is the
unchanging
changer, the healer of
humankind. As I
close, if there are those people today
who
say there was an altar called, hundreds
of people came to the Lord. But if you
say,
"Mut,
hi, I want to receive the Lord today.
I could not come to the first altar call
maybe but I want you to pray for me.
Stand on your
feet. Never allow the moment to
pass. Never allow any moment to pass.
Stand on your feet. And if you don't
mind, if you don't
mind, I don't I don't I don't worry. I
don't it doesn't matter how many you are
but I want you to run because this is a
soccer place. Run and stand in front of
me. I want to say two words over you.
Run to Jesus right now. Run to Jesus.
Don't focus on your enemies. Don't focus
on the things that have happened in your
life.
You've come with a
friend. I ask
you because God has a set purpose for
your life. Come and stand here. I want
to pray for you. Let's give God a big
hands of praise for those who are coming
uh for the Lord Jesus Christ is ready
for your life. Come, come, come
everybody. Come, come, come and receive
Jesus. Look at that. Look at that. Look
at that. Look at that. Look at that.
They are still coming. Encourage them.
Encourage them. Clap hands for them.
Encourage them. They are coming. They
are coming. They are coming. If you are
young, you can run. Run to Jesus. Run to
Jesus. Run to Jesus. Your life will
never be the same again. Your life will
never be the same
again. My
God, heaven is
rejoicing. Hell is
crying. We are populating heaven.
Look at that young man how he's running
to Jesus. I can tell you he's free. I
can tell you he's free. Look at the
young ones who are running to Jesus.
Luke the 14 years. Luke the 14. Luke the
12 years. They can hear the gospel. The
Bible says the gospel unto all nations
for a witness. Look at that. Look at
that. The young
[Applause]
ones run with run to Jesus. Run. Forget
about yourself. Run run
run run run
run
[Music]
[Applause]
run to Jesus.
Run to the King of
Kings. Run to the Lord of
Lords. Run to
Jesus. Run to the Savior.
[Music]
Hey, they're still coming. They're still
coming. Today is the day of your
salvation. Today is the day of your
salvation.
Today is the day that you meet your
creator. Today is the day that you meet
the Lord. Look at Look the young
ones. Look at the young ones. They run.
Run to
Jesus. Run to Jesus. Run to the
Savior. He will save you. Your life will
never be the same again.
In the name of
Jesus. In the name of
Jesus. In the name of Jesus. Look look
look at this. Look at this. They are not
tired. Hallelujah.
And and those who are healed, those who
have a testimony of healing, stand
aside. Those who have a testimony of
healing, stand the sight so that we can
see that you have a testimony of
healing. On this side, on this side.
You are still running to
Jesus. People are running to the things
of the world. But you are running to
Jesus. You are running to salvation. You
are running to eternal life.
[Music]
to the
malif. Oh
hallelujah. Oh
hallelujah. Come on to Jesus. Come on.
Come on. Come on to Jesus. Come to
Jesus. He's waiting for you. Come to
Jesus. Come to Jesus. Come to Jesus.
Come to Jesus. He's waiting for you.
Come to the King of Kings. Come to the
Savior is waiting for you. In the name
of
Jesus. In the name of
Jesus. In Jesus
name. Thank you Lord Jesus.
I'm
waiting. I see. I see you.
Yes. My name
[Music]
Hallelujah. Hallelujah. Let's give the
Lord a big hand for all the
people. Hallelujah.
[Applause]
prophet that
today you've
responded and whatever Satan wanted to
do in your life, God changes all of
that. So, you've come today to invite
Christ in your life. Let me pray for
you. Lord, we thank you for
these your children. learn
today. And we know as they receive
Christ, you bring about a change in
their life, a
transformation, and you give them a new
life. We thank you for your word, and we
give you praise in Jesus name. And
everybody
[Music]
said just for a few
minutes because towards the
end. All right. So you must come back
quickly. All right. So just turn to your
left outside there. Just turn to your
left quickly and back into the
auditorium. Just follow
give them a big hand as they go just
[Music]
[Applause]
now. All
right. So, as they leave, I don't want
us in any
way to not realize how God touched
people's lives.
You know,
as prophet was
praying and speaking by God's word of
knowledge, those of you who knew you had
those
conditions, just know that
God has touched your life
today. Yeah, I think you must give the
Lord a hand. Just know that God has
touched your life today.
Just know
that God is the one who
changes, touches
lives, changes people's lives, transform
people's lives. Sometimes people come
into the service, God touches their
life, but they're not even aware God has
touched
them. Check
yourself. Check what God has
done. Examine yourself.
Because many times God touches people
and people are just not aware of it.
Prophet we want to thank the Lord for
you sir. You have another service and so
on. We just want to thank you for coming
and for
sacrificing man of God. God bless you
sir. Let's give the Lord a big big hand
for the prophet as he goes.
Amen. Hallelujah.